distilled.co.uk 2019-06-25

# Distilled Privacy Policy

This privacy notice tells you about the information we collect from you when you use our website www.distilled.net. In collecting this information, we are acting as a data controller and, by law, we are required to provide you with information about us, about why and how we use your data, and about the rights you have over your data.

## Who are we?

We are Distilled Ltd. Our address is 4th Floor, Chapter House, 18-20 Crucifix Lane, London, SE1 3JW. You can contact us by post at the above address, by email at info@distilled.net or by telephone on +44 (0)20 71830767.

We are not required to have a data protection officer, so any enquiries about our use of your personal data should be addressed to the contact details above.

## How we use your information

  * When you use our website
  * When you submit an enquiry via our website
  * When you purchase a product from our website
  * When you sign up to receive our newsletter
  * When you download a sample document
  * When you apply for a job with Distilled
  * Your rights as a data subject
  * Your right to complain
  * Updates to this privacy policy

## When you use our website

When you use our website to browse our products and services and view the information we make available, a number of cookies are used by us and by third parties to allow the website to function, to collect useful information about visitors and to help to make your user experience better.

## When you submit an enquiry via our website

When you submit an enquiry via our website, we ask you for your name, contact telephone number and email address.

We use this information to respond to your query, including providing you with any requested information about our products and services. We may also email you several times after your enquiry in order to follow up on your interest and ensure that we have answered your it to your satisfaction. We will do this based on our legitimate interest in providing accurate information prior to a sale.

Your enquiry is stored and processed as an email. It is also logged on a CRM system.

We do not use the information you provide to make any automated decisions that might affect you.

## When you purchase a product from our website

When you purchase products from us online, we ask you for your name, address, contact telephone number, email address and credit card information. We also record your IP (Internet Protocol) address, which is the address of your computer on the Internet.

We will use your information to verify your credit card details for your purchase, process your order and to send you your products. We will also send you a receipt via email and we may use your telephone number to contact you regarding your purchase.

We require this information in order to process your payment, deliver your products or services and fulfil our contract with you. We record your IP address in order to show that the correct tax was applied to the sale, which we are required to do by law.

Your information is stored on our website and on our cloud server, both of which are based within the European Union. Your credit card details are passed to a third-party payment processor. We do not retain your credit card information. 

We do not use the information you provide to make any automated decisions that might affect you.

We keep your order information for an indefinite period, as the licenses we sell for our products do not expire.

## When you sign up to receive our newsletter

When you sign up to receive our newsletter, we ask for your name and your email address.  
We will ask for your consent to use your name and email address to email you our newsletter which contains information about our products and other information which we feel might be of interest to you.

You can withdraw your consent at any time and we will stop sending you the newsletter.  
We do not use the information you provide to make any automated decisions that might affect you.

## When you download a sample document

When you request to download a sample document, such as a white paper, we ask for your name, company name (which is optional) and your email address.

We use this information to email you a link to download the requested document. We may also email you after your download in order to follow up on your interest in our products and services. We will do this based on our legitimate interest in marketing to prospects for our products and services.

We do not use the information you provide to make any automated decisions that might affect you.

## When you apply for a job with Distilled

When you apply for a job with Distilled, we ask you for your name, contact telephone number and email address along with other information associated with a job application.

We use this information to contact you about your application. We may also follow up with you later about alternative roles that we feel could be a good fit if your initial application is unsuccessful. We will do this based on our legitimate interest in evaluating the possibility of working together.

Your enquiry is stored and processed as an email. It is also logged on an Applicant Tracking System (ATS).

We do not use the information you provide to make any automated decisions that might affect you.

## Your rights as a data subject

By law, you can ask us what information we hold about you, and you can ask us to correct it if it is inaccurate. If we have asked for your consent to process your personal data, you may withdraw that consent at any time.

If we are processing your personal data for reasons of consent or to fulfil a contract, you can ask us to give you a copy of the information in a machine-readable format so that you can transfer it to another provider.

If we are processing your personal data for reasons of consent or legitimate interest, you can request that your data be erased.

You have the right to ask us to stop using your information for a period of time if you believe we are not doing so lawfully.

Finally, in some circumstances you can ask us not to reach decisions affecting you using automated processing or profiling.

To submit a request regarding your personal data by email, post or telephone, please use the contact information provided above in the Who Are We section of this policy.

## Your right to complain

If you have a complaint about our use of your information, we would prefer you to contact us directly in the first instance so that we can address your complaint. However, you can also contact the Information Commissioner’s Office via their website at www.ico.org.uk/concerns or write to them.

## Updates to this privacy policy

We regularly review and, if appropriate, update this privacy policy from time to time, and as our services and use of personal data evolves. If we want to make use of your personal data in a way that we haven’t previously identified, we will contact you to provide information about this and, if necessary, to ask for your consent.

This is version 2.2. Last updated on 24th May 2018. We will update the version number and date of this document each time it is changed.
